[
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 40,
  "Task": "9901_0036_d_00_container_masterofthetempest",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9919_MSQ_WardenScout",
  "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_36",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_35 || 99D_MSQ_08",
  "RequiredLevel": 0,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_objective_title",
  "Description": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": false,
  "HideAvailableMapIcon ": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "9901_0057_insoulinstone",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "9901_0057_d_00_container_insoulinstone",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0717_Warden",
  "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_57",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_56 || 99E_MSQ_11",
  "RequiredLevel": 0,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0057_insoulinstone_success",
  "ItemRewardName": "QuestReward_MSQFinale",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "9910_0057_insoulinstone_objective_title",
  "Description": "9910_0057_insoulinstone_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "9910_0057_insoulinstone_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "9910_0057_insoulinstone_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "9910_0057_insoulinstone_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "9910_0057_insoulinstone_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": true,
  "HideAvailableMapIcon ": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "9910_0058_finallyexhale",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "9910_0058_d_00_container_finallyexhale",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9905e_MSQ_Rima",
  "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_58",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_57",
  "RequiredLevel": 0,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "9910_0058_finallyexhale_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "9910_0058_finallyexhale_objective_title",
  "Description": "9910_0058_finallyexhale_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "9910_0058_finallyexhale_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "9910_0058_finallyexhale_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "9910_0058_finallyexhale_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "9910_0058_finallyexhale_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": true,
  "HideAvailableMapIcon ": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "9905_0059_InMemoriam",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "9910_0059_d_00_container_InMemoriam",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9928_MSQ_YonasMemorial",
  "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_59",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_58",
  "RequiredLevel": 0,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0059_InMemoriam_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "9905_0059_InMemoriam_objective_title",
  "Description": "9905_0059_InMemoriam_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "9905_0059_InMemoriam_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "9905_0059_InMemoriam_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "9905_0059_InMemoriam_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "9905_0059_InMemoriam_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": true,
  "HideAvailableMapIcon ": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "9926_0101_TenaciousRose",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 20,
  "Task": "9926_0101_d_00_container_TenaciousRose",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9926_VK_AbigailRoseB",
  "AchievementId": "VarangianKnights_0101",
  "RequiredLevel": 0,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "9926_0101_TenaciousRose_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "9926_0101_TenaciousRose_objective_title",
  "Description": "9926_0101_TenaciousRose_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "9926_0101_TenaciousRose_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "9926_0101_TenaciousRose_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "9926_0101_TenaciousRose_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "9926_0101_TenaciousRose_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": false,
  "HideAvailableMapIcon ": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "9926_0103_LostScarecrow",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 28,
  "Task": "9926_0103_d_00_container_LostScarecrow",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9930_VK_RomacBarboB",
  "AchievementId": "VarangianKnights_0103",
  "RequiredLevel": 0,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "9926_0103_LostScarecrow_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "9926_0103_LostScarecrow_objective_title",
  "Description": "9926_0103_LostScarecrow_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "9926_0103_LostScarecrow_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "9926_0103_LostScarecrow_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "9926_0103_LostScarecrow_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "9926_0103_LostScarecrow_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": false,
  "HideAvailableMapIcon ": false
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "9932_0104_RelicReclamation",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 30,
  "Task": "9932_0104_d_00_container_RelicReclamation",
  "NpcDestinationId": "9931_VK_Caoimhe",
  "AchievementId": "VarangianKnights_0104",
  "RequiredLevel": 0,
  "SuccessGameEventId": "9932_0104_RelicReclamation_success",
  "ItemRewardQty": 0,
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "9932_0104_RelicReclamation_objective_title",
  "Description": "9932_0104_RelicReclamation_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "9932_0104_RelicReclamation_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "9932_0104_RelicReclamation_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "9932_0104_RelicReclamation_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "9932_0104_RelicReclamation_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
  "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": false,
  "HideAvailableMapIcon ": true
 }
]